[{"question":"which object is bigger?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wood cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the large cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Wood"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Brick"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the small RedUnknown cube heavier than the large wood cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small RedUnknown cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large wood cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small RedUnknown cube travel to quadrant \u2163?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large wood cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small RedUnknown cube collide with the large wood cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small marble cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large wood cube and the small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large wood cube and the small marble cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small marble cube and the wall"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large wood cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small redunknown cube and the large wood cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small redunknown cube and the wall"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small RedUnknown cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]